JASEEL K T

UI UX DEVELOPER CUM DESIGNER

PROFILE

UI Developer with 9 years of experience creating streamlined and intuitive controls through programming and design. To be a part of a growth oriented organization, contributing, Learning and enhancing my development both as a professional and as an individual.

EXPERIENCE

Smart management it solutions | Qatar

UI/UX Cum UI Developer - From Feb 2017 to Present

- Design, Develop & Implement Web Applications
- Developing interactive wireframes, HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript page development
- Browser compatibility and cross platform testing, prototyping, and implementation

Pink Lemonade Communications Pvt Ltd | Bangalore

UI Developer - From May 2015 to Feb 2017

- Used wireframes, mock-ups and prototypes to establish user interface design.
- Build highly functional website using JavaScript, HTML and CSS.
- Wordpress template design and development

Logicshore | Bangalore

UI Designer / Developer - From October 2014 to May 2015

- Enhanced functionality and appearance of website and repaired functionality issues.
- Wordpress template design and development

Zolipe Solutions Pvt Ltd | Bangalore

Web Designer - From September 2013 to September 2014

- Preparing web templates using Adobe Photoshop
- PSD to HTML conversion, using HTML, CSS
- Day to day maintenance of website



+91 8951478742 jaseelkt09@gmail.com Whitefield, Bangalore

EDUCATION

2006 - Kerala

S.S.L.C

2008 - Kerala

Plus Two

2011 - Calicut University
B.com

2011 - Arena , Bangalore Web & Interactive Design

LANGUAGE

- English
- Hindi
- Malayalam

SKILLS

- HTML
- CSS
- Javascript
- Jquery
- Bootstrap
- Wordpress
- Adobe XD
- Uxpin